[Music]
hello everybody it is nicole from
kiwi and today we'll be reviewing the
coloria alcohol marker set
and the mandala coloring book that was
kindly gifted to me
so let's not waste any time and hop
right into the video
amazon seems to be the only place to
purchase these so for the marker set
it is 22.99 and the mandala coloring
book is 15.99
for the packaging the alcohol marker set
comes in a clear plastic carrying case
there is a snap closure on the front and
a handle on the top
the markers inside are kind of loose so
there's some empty space
so they move around and you can't really
keep them in a particular order because
of this
as for the coloring book it is spiral
bound and an a4
size the marker set comes with 41
markers total
with 40 colored markers and one
colorless blender
each marker comes with the fine tip on
one side
marked with a gray band and on the other
side is a chisel or broad tip
on the cap of the marker the name and
number can be found
as well as a color swatch in my set
i actually received a duplicate of a
pink marker
and when i looked through their swatches
online i realized the color i was
missing was magenta
and i got a duplicate of a color called
true pink
i don't think this was intentional and i
could see that magenta would look
similar to the true pink color
for the swatches the order was based on
numerical order
the set has a good variation within each
color so there's several shades of each
color
for example there's at least three
purples and
different shades of green and the colors
are very bright and saturated
especially after one layer
as for the coloring book it comes with
30 nature inspired mandalas
which include flowers animals insects
and even fairies
they also have another mandala coloring
book available which is more just
mandalas but i chose this one because of
the animals
all the pages are single-sided on thick
smooth paper
and coloring the mandala was actually
pretty therapeutic
i've never really done it before but i
can definitely see the appeal
i also wanted to test the paper and make
sure it didn't bleed
because it did say it was bleed
resistant so i put a piece of paper
behind the one i was coloring just in
case but when i finished
to my surprise the marker did not bleed
at all
onto the next page even when i applied
several layers of marker in some areas
that didn't bleed through either
for the pros i think that the marker set
is very portable
especially because it comes with a
carrying case that has a handle so you
can take it with you on the go
i like that there is a good variety of
each color even though it's a small set
there is some variation within each
color group
i found that the markers blend very well
together
and the markers also work very well on
the coloring book there's no bleeding
or feathering
as for the cons there was a bit of
feathering on the mermaid drawing that i
did
definitely not a crisp line because it
was on different paper
i did use something that had a little
bit more tooth to it
so if you have something that's more
textured and not smooth
then i think you can expect some
feathering
another con is that i did receive a
duplicate as i mentioned earlier
but i do think that it was an honest
mistake and i don't think every single
set is going to have
a mistake like that i think it's kind of
funny that it actually happened to me
before
with a different company and their
marker set so maybe i'm just doomed to
have
duplicates of markers
[Music]
and the last con is that the colors
included are very saturated and bright
which made it a little bit difficult to
come up with a color scheme
but i did manage and actually like the
color scheme of this mermaid
i just feel like with this set there's
definitely a lot more
bright colors compared to pale tones and
darker
tones to add contrast
overall i do think this would be a good
addition to a marker collection
because the colors are so saturated that
it could be added to a collection
that has more hues and different tones
or you can use this with the coloring
books as i mentioned earlier in the pros
the markers work really great with the
coloring book and i can imagine it being
a really great gift set
idea for someone who likes coloring
books since these two
pair so well together i hope you found
this video
useful or helpful in any way if you did
and want to see
more videos like this be sure to hit
that subscribe button
and ring the bell so you're notified of
when i post a new video
so with that i want to thank you all so
much for joining me today
keep drawing keep creating and i'll see
you all next time
bye
you